So hello everyone welcome back to our channel
in this video we are going to talk about the
new vacancy of ICC Bank so let us tell you all
that ICC Bank has
released the notification of new vacancy
for which candidates from all over India
can apply,
in this video we will share with you all the complete information about
how you can apply,
what will be the selection process, what is the criteria, so
if you want to apply for the job of the bank then
you must watch this video till the end
so that you all get the complete information
and if you like the video then please
like, share the video and subscribe to the channel
so that you get the notification of every update coming in the future
first,
you apply for many jobs
and if you are not getting a reply back,
if you are upset with this then
you should definitely register on this website,
here you all can get one of the
best jobs and that too for free, you
all have to follow only two steps,
first file your basic information here
You have to upload your resume here.
First, this entire process will be
free of cost for you. I have given the link for this
in the description of the video. I will
inform you all when you
can register here. When updates start coming directly according to your
qualification criteria, it is
possible
that when you get it with its help, the
link has been given in the description of the video.
You can go there and do clear registration for it.
Now let's talk about your
new vacancy of ICC Bank.
Online
application forms have started for this, so
any eligible candidate from all over India can
go to its official recruitment website and
apply the online application form. Otherwise,
you should not use any other mode. Even
if you do, your application form will be
rejected. Therefore, you should apply for
it only from its official recruitment website.
Here,
information has been given to you about some banks, which you
can check here and all the candidates already
know about this.  Also, if
we talk about the post in vacancy here,
how many vacancies have been
announced here, then let us tell you all that 30500
plus vacancies have been announced here and if we
talk about the name of the post and
department here, like yours is
PO, yours is Relationship Manager,
yours is Assistant Manager Operation and the Single
Window Club Marketing Security
Criteria, then first of all let us tell you all that
in the limit section, all those candidates who have completed 18 plus
can apply for it.
Your minimum criteria has been kept at 18 years,
in the maximum section you have not been
told, for the post you will also
apply, you get to see the qualification criteria for the specific post,
apart from this, if we talk about the education
qualification section here, then 10th
pass, 12th pass and graduate candidates
can apply for it, you have any  You have
completed your creation etc. in Sarita,
you have completed your studies,
you can apply for it.
Talking about salary, your minimum starting salary is 26000 rupees
and here
your salary is expected to be 45000 per month. It
depends on your qualification
criteria and for which post you are
selected, how your interview
goes, all these things. Also, if we talk about
location, Across India has
branches. Let me tell you all,
when you can get a location across India, you can get it
near your city. If we talk about it, then
here you will have full
time permanent employment. Any
pre-trained candidate can apply for it, be it
male or female candidate. Also, if we
talk about the selection process,
then here you will be selected only on interview basis,
and those candidates who
qualify the interview, then after this their
documentation is done. Here some short
details are for all of you.  It is given which you
can see on the screen. Many
candidates have doubts whether they have to pay any
application fee here or not.
So I will tell you all that you who belong to
any
category in Over India, you do
not have to pay any application fee,
you can register for it free of cost. If
you want to apply, then to apply, you have to read out the
complete guidelines on this official recruitment website
and apply for it.
All male and female candidates from Over India can
apply.
To apply, you can apply online from its official website.
Some
important dates have been mentioned here, such as
its online application form has started from 19th July 2023
and
you can register for it till 22nd August 2023,
so go quickly and register for it.
Along with this,
some important links have been given to all of you here, so you can
apply.  You all will also get the link to
apply, so search the
website you are seeing on the screen in Google browser, let us
tell you the further process, first of all
whatever device you use, whether
you have a mobile, laptop or desktop,
you will open Google browser in it and
here you will have to search study per
dreams.in, so you all have to search this website, as
soon as you search this website,
you will get the result at the top,
study per dreams learn per future first, the
link which you are seeing, as soon as
you click on it,
this type of interface of some website opens in front of you,
where you can see that
you get to see the notification of ICC Bank first,
along with these, if you do
not get to see this notification, then
a search button has been given on the top right side,
where you can find it from it
and as soon as you click on the notification,
its detailed notification
opens in front of you, so
I have already shared its details with all of you,
but if you still have any doubt or
query, then you can confirm it here,
to apply you will find it below  If you want to
scroll, then as you scroll,
you will see the apply online form by clicking here. This
link is the first one. As soon as you click on the link,
you will see that you are
directed to the official recruitment website of ICC Bank, where you
can search for any item and can also search by applying filters.
You also get to see other options in
which you can see that
this vacancy has been announced in relation management and retail banking, in
which you should have 3 to 10 years of experience.
Also, a vacancy has been announced for phone banking officer
because it will be in sales and
relationship, in which 0 to 6 years of
experience has been asked. Your
location will be in Guwahati, Chennai, Indore, Hyderabad and
Thane. Also, you
can see the vacancy for PO, in which
your experience of zero to one year has been asked. So in
this way, you will get to see many more in
which you can see that
here there are vacancies for credit and policy,
which are vacancies for the whole of India.
Across India for which there should be zero to six years
of experience and any
candidate can apply for it, so
this vacancy of credit manager has been announced in
this way, you can check many vacancies here
and
you can apply for whichever vacancy you are eligible for,
so here is wholesale banking,
for which you
find the qualification criteria appropriate, like wholesale
banking is given here, so when you
click on the title,
after clicking, a detailed notification opens in front of you,
which will give you all the details
of what qualification is required, it should be there here,
so any candidate
can apply, the complete
responsibility etc. is told to all of you here,
along with the minimum
maximum here, it is zero, that is,
pressure candidates can also apply, you can
see the location, it is cross India location, there are
vacancies for the whole of India and below
you get the option, click here, that is,
apply here  As soon as you
click on Apply, some applicant
login details open in front of you. If you are
applying for the first time from here, then first of all
you have to click on New User i.e. Sign Up.
As soon as you
click on Sign Up, after clicking on Sign Up,
a new window opens in front of you in
which your profile sheet will open in which
your complete registration page will be opened in which first of all
your uploaded resume personal
details are there, then there is your academy
information, then there is your experience
and then in the last there is your
supplementary information. When you
complete this information, then
you can simply apply for any vacancy here. It is a
very simple process. The
answer here is that if you file the basic details
here, then you can
directly apply for any vacancy by logging in with C.
So this is the process of
applying for ICC Bank,
so I have shared the entire process with all of you.
Also, if you have any
problem regarding this, then  If you are not getting it then
you are getting a free opportunity, the
link of which I have given in the description of the video.
Simply you have to follow two steps,
register and upload your resume.
After this,
when updates will start coming to you directly,
if you apply for it, then it is
possible that when you get a shortlist from there, then
you can apply from that. I hope the
entire information must have become clear to all of you
and you must have liked the video. If you
liked the video, then please
like and share the video and subscribe to the channel
and press the bell icon so that you keep getting the
notification of every update coming in the future. You will meet
in the next video. So thank you but keep
watching. Jai Hind Jai Bharat.